Everyone tells you to learn from native speakers.
We think that's wrong.
Learn from the native speaker who already thinks like you.
You don't think in English. You already know how you think.
The hard part is expressing those same thoughts in another language.
We don't analyze your vocabulary.
We analyze how you build ideas.
Then we verify every claim.
Only then
we look for the best role model.
They don't use the same words.
They use the same way of thinking.
GPT-5.6 doesn't analyze your English.
It reasons about how you organize ideas.
Codex helped us build and iterate on the system.
Instead of searching through millions of videos, you discover the one person
who already explains the world the way your mind understands it.
And it runs both ways. Even a small creator can come here —
to be discovered by the exact people who already think the way they explain the world.
Today, we help you find someone who already thinks like you.
Tomorrow, we might understand how you learn well enough to help you become someone else's role model.